<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Intro on tricky42</title>
    <link>https://www.bucksteeg.de/tags/intro/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Intro on tricky42</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Andreas Bucksteeg; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://www.bucksteeg.de/tags/intro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome!</title>
      <link>https://www.bucksteeg.de/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 23:12:02 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bucksteeg.de/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Hugo is written in Go with support for multiple platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The latest release can be found at Hugo Releases. We currently provide pre-built binaries for  Windows,  Linux,  FreeBSD and  OS X (Darwin) for x64, i386 and ARM architectures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hugo may also be compiled from source wherever the Go compiler tool chain can run, e.g. for other operating systems including DragonFly BSD, OpenBSD, Plan 9 and Solaris. See &lt;a href=&#34;http://golang.org/doc/install/source&#34;&gt;http://golang.org/doc/install/source&lt;/a&gt; for the full set of supported combinations of target operating systems and compilation architectures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;installing-hugo-binary&#34;&gt;Installing Hugo (binary)&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Installation is very easy. Simply download the appropriate version for your platform from Hugo Releases. Once downloaded it can be run from anywhere. You don’t need to install it into a global location. This works well for shared hosts and other systems where you don’t have a privileged account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ideally, you should install it somewhere in your PATH for easy use. /usr/local/bin is the most probable location.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On OS X, if you have Homebrew, installation is even easier: just run brew update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; brew install hugo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a more detailed explanation follow the corresponding installation guides:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Installation on OS X
Installation on Windows
Installing Pygments (optional)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Hugo executable has one optional external dependency for source code highlighting (Pygments).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to have source code highlighting using the highlight shortcode, you need to install the Python-based Pygments program. The procedure is outlined on the Pygments home page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upgrading Hugo&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upgrading Hugo is as easy as downloading and replacing the executable you’ve placed in your PATH.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Installing from source&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prerequisite tools for downloading and building source code&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Git
Go 1.5+
Get directly from GitHub&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$ export GOPATH=$HOME/go
$ go get -v github.com/spf13/hugo
go get will then fetch Hugo and all its dependent libraries to your $GOPATH/src directory, and compile everything into the final hugo (or hugo.exe) executable, which you will find sitting in the $GOPATH/bin/ directory, all ready to go!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may run go get with the -u option to update Hugo’s dependencies:&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>